	1.	Edit the assignment files with your solutions
	2.	Add your changes to the repository: git add .
	3.	Commit your changes: git commit -m "My solutions to (what you are working on, e.g., lab 1.1)"
	4.	Push your changes to your fork: git push origin master
	5.	Make a pull request by going to https://github.com/deepesch/DSCI6002-student and clicking "Pull Requests" and then "New Pull Request". Then click "Create Pull Request". Put your name in the pull request title and then click "Create Pull Request" again.
